=The Queen of Attack=
=ملكة الهجوم=
=Episode 19=
=الحلقة 19=
Night after night,
ليلة بعد ليلة،
watching over her in silence.
يراقبها في صمت.
All mute.
كلهم صامتون.
I'll wake her up.
سأوقظها.
You can't wake her.
لا يمكنك إيقاظها.
She's pretending.
إنها تتظاهر.
Pretending is better.
التظاهر أفضل.
At least this way,
على الأقل بهذه الطريقة،
I can stay by her side forever.
أستطيع البقاء بجانبها إلى الأبد.
(Prince Rui's Mansion)
(قصر الأمير روي)
Hong'er, where are you?
هونغ إير، أين أنت؟
Hong'er.
هونغ'ر.
You found me!
لقد وجدتني!
You're amazing!
أنت مذهلة!
So impressive!
مثير للإعجاب للغاية!
Young lady.
سيدة شابة.
Young lady,
سيدة شابة،
don't leave.
لا تغادر.
Hello,
مرحبًا،
I'm Lin Hong'er.
أنا لين هونغ إير.
Lady Lin.
السيدة لين.
This is Xiao Xian, the Prince Heir.
هذا هو شياو شيان، ولي العهد الأمير.
You two make a perfect pair.
أنتم الاثنان تشكلان زوجًا مثاليًا.
Why stay?
لماذا البقاء؟
You're no needed here.
لا حاجة لك هنا.
Liuyun.
ليويون.
I...
أنا...
She's not lying.
إنها لا تكذب.
Do you like him?
هل تحبه؟
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
Do you like her too?
هل تحبها أيضا؟
The one I like
الذي يعجبني
is Lin Hong'er.
إنها لين هونغ إير.
Good! Good!
جيد! جيد!
I am Lin Hong'er.
أنا لين هونغ إير.
(Prince Rui's Mansion)
(قصر الأمير روي)
(The one I like)
(الذي يعجبني)
is Lin Hong'er.
إنها لين هونغ إير.
Heaven's justice prevails.
عدالة السماء تسود.
(May the guilty be punished.)
( فليُعاقب المذنبون)
(Here rest Lin Sanjiang and his wife) (May the departed rest in peace.)
(هنا يرقد لين سانجيانج وزوجته) (رحم الله المرحومين).
A person's appearance
مظهر الشخص
can't be completely altered.
لا يمكن تغييرها بالكامل.
Xiao Xian mentioned
ذكر شياو شيان
the County Princess studied unorthodox medical techniques.
درست أميرة المقاطعة تقنيات طبية غير تقليدية.
(Medical Book)
(كتاب طبي)
The Flesh Worm
دودة اللحم
can make one's appearance
يمكن أن يظهر المرء
change drastically.
تغير جذريا.
Hong'er.
هونغ'ر.
Why have you changed, Hong'er?
لماذا تغيرت، هونغ إير؟
Who's in there?
من هناك؟
County Princess's library
مكتبة مقاطعة الأميرة
is off-limits to all.
ممنوع على الجميع.
Keep watch.
ابقى حذرا.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Hong Linlang...
هونج لينلانج...
Lin Hong'er...
لين هونغ إير...
Hong Linlang is Lin Hong'er.
هونغ لينلانغ هو لين هونغ إير.
Aren't you mad?
ألا أنت مجنون؟
It looks smooth and delicate,
يبدو سلسًا وحساسًا،
but upon touch,
ولكن عند اللمس،
there seem to be layers of scars
يبدو أن هناك طبقات من الندوب
hidden beneath this delicate skin.
مخفية تحت هذا الجلد الرقيق.
I'm not Lin Hong'er.
أنا لست لين هونغ إير.
You are.
أنت.
What?
ماذا؟
Planning your defense?
هل تخطط للدفاع عن نفسك؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm Lin Hong'er.
أنا لين هونغ إير.
Though I look nothing like her,
على الرغم من أنني لا أشبهها في أي شيء،
I am her essence.
أنا جوهرها.
Why would I need defense?
لماذا أحتاج للدفاع؟
Don't forget
لا تنسى
you're currently a madwoman.
أنت امرأة مجنونة حاليًا.
Such horrific claims
مثل هذه الادعاءات المروعة
coming from a lunatic
قادمة من مجنون
will only make people think
سوف يجعل الناس يفكرون فقط
you're truly mad.
أنت مجنون حقا.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I'm a madwoman.
أنا امرأة مجنونة.
No one believes a madwoman's words.
لا أحد يصدق كلام المجنونة.
None will believe.
لن يصدق أحد.
No one ever believes...
لا أحد يصدق أبدًا...
What's her true purpose here?
ما هو هدفها الحقيقي هنا؟
I'm such a fool.
أنا أحمق جدًا.
I failed to recognize you as Lin Hong'er.
لقد فشلت في التعرف عليك باعتبارك لين هونغ إير.
I failed to recognize you.
لقد فشلت في التعرف عليك.
(I interrogated those jailers.)
(استجوبت هؤلاء السجانين).
(Under Magistrate He Laijin's orders,)
(بناءً على أوامر القاضي هي لايجين)
(they used inhuman methods to torture Lin Hong'er)
(لقد استخدموا أساليب غير إنسانية لتعذيب لين هونغ إير)
(to extract every detail of her encounters with you.)
(لاستخراج كل تفاصيل لقاءاتها معك.)
(So Xu Ziyi could impersonate her perfectly.)
(لذلك يمكن لـ Xu Ziyi تقليدها بشكل مثالي.)
(Testimony)
(شهادة)
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
You've returned, Your Highness.
لقد عدت يا صاحب السمو.
Stop pretending madness.
توقف عن التظاهر بالجنون.
Kill me.
اقتلني.
Instead of living burdened by sin,
بدلا من العيش مثقلا بالخطيئة،
I might as well die in your hand.
ربما من الأفضل أن أموت في يدك.
You truly deserve to die.
أنت تستحق الموت حقًا.
Do you know what she's been through?
هل تعلم ماذا مرت به؟
Do you know how much she's suffered?
هل تعلم كم عانت؟
Do you think my life has been any better?
هل تعتقد أن حياتي أصبحت أفضل؟
Do you think my heart
هل تعتقد أن قلبي
hasn't been tormented day and night?
لم يتعذب ليلًا ونهارًا؟
Do you know the only thing I can't let go of?
هل تعلم ما هو الشيء الوحيد الذي لا أستطيع التخلي عنه؟
It's that I genuinely love you.
إنني أحبك بصدق.
What pains me most
ما يؤلمني أكثر
is that I deceived you.
هو أنني خدعتك.
That's why I chose
لهذا السبب اخترت
to let you discover the truth.
لتسمح لك باكتشاف الحقيقة.
My only wish is that after I die,
أمنيتي الوحيدة هي أنه بعد أن أموت،
you can reunite with her.
يمكنك أن تلتقي بها مرة أخرى.
Why?
لماذا؟
Killing you
قتلك
would only dirty my sword.
لن يؤدي إلا إلى تلويث سيفي.
Since that's the case,
وبما أن هذه هي الحالة،
let me live to atone for my sins.
دعني أعيش لأكفر عن خطاياي.
I heard Lin Hong'er is faking her pregnancy.
سمعت أن لين هونغ إير تتظاهر بالحمل.
If that's true,
إذا كان هذا صحيحا،
she'll surely be executed.
سيتم اعدامها بالتأكيد.
Take her away from the mansion immediately.
خذها بعيدًا عن القصر فورًا.
Flee far away.
اهرب بعيدا.
Your Highness, you got great taste.
صاحب السمو، لديك ذوق رائع.
Pearls?
اللؤلؤ؟
Are these all?
هل هذه كلها؟
Yes.
نعم.
Are we really
هل نحن حقا
proceeding with this marriage?
المضي قدما في هذا الزواج؟
My mother had two children.
كان لدى والدتي طفلين.
One was the late Prince Rui,
وكان أحدهم الأمير الراحل روي،
and the other is me.
والآخر هو أنا.
So Prince Xian's father was...
لذا كان والد الأمير شيان...
An illegitimate child of unknown birth.
طفل غير شرعي من مواليد مجهولين.
That's why both the late Prince Rui and I hold titles,
ولهذا السبب، أنا والأمير الراحل روي نحمل ألقابًا،
but Xiao Xian's father
لكن والد شياو شيان
was just a commoner.
كان مجرد شخص عادي.
If Prince Xian marries a mad wife,
إذا تزوج الأمير شيان من زوجة مجنونة،
His Majesty will never let him inherit the title.
جلالته لن يسمح له بالحصول على اللقب أبدًا.
But what if Lady Hong's child isn't a son?
ولكن ماذا لو لم يكن طفل السيدة هونغ ابنًا؟
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
Very good.
جيد جدًا.
Take a look.
خذ نظرة.
Pick what you like.
اختر ما يعجبك
Don't eat this.
لا تأكل هذا.
Prince Xian, you're here.
الأمير شيان، أنت هنا.
Perfect timing.
توقيت مثالي.
Let's review the list together.
دعونا نراجع القائمة معًا.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
I'll handle it.
سأتعامل مع الأمر.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
let's review over there.
دعونا نراجع هناك.
Come.
يأتي.
This side has a better view.
هذا الجانب لديه رؤية أفضل.
Hurry.
عجل.
Come on.
تعال.
Sit here.
اجلس هنا.
Look,
ينظر،
we've prepared many items.
لقد قمنا بإعداد العديد من العناصر.
Sit down.
اجلس.
Enough.
كافٍ.
This is women's business.
هذا عمل المرأة.
You shouldn't stay here.
لا ينبغي عليك البقاء هنا.
Great.
عظيم.
I need to speak with Lady Hong.
أريد أن أتحدث مع السيدة هونغ.
I'll take my leave.
سوف آخذ إجازتي.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
I suddenly feel unwell.
أشعر فجأة بالتوعك.
I must excuse myself.
يجب أن أعتذر عن نفسي.
Stop!
قف!
Your fiancée is mad.
خطيبك مجنون.
Does that mean you can publicly
هل هذا يعني أنه يمكنك علناً
discard all decency?
التخلي عن كل الحشمة؟
You and my father are sworn enemies.
أنت وأبي أعداء لدودون.
I've known it since childhood.
لقد عرفت ذلك منذ الطفولة.
Your purpose in coming here
هدفك من المجيء إلى هنا
is to keep me from inheriting the title, isn't it?
هل هذا منعني من وراثة اللقب؟
If I lose face,
إذا فقدت وجهي،
doesn't that serve your purpose?
ألا يخدم هذا غرضك؟
You...
أنت...
- Let go of me! - Listen to me!
-اتركني! -استمع لي!
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I beg you. Listen to me!
أتوسل إليك، استمع لي!
Listen!
يستمع!
I know everything now.
أنا أعرف كل شيء الآن.
♪Rain-chilled frost on midnight drear♪
???الصقيع المثلج بالمطر في منتصف الليل الكئيب ???
♪Your honeyed lies still sear my ear♪
???أكاذيبك المعسولة لا تزال تؤلم أذني؟؟؟
♪I carved your face in memory's sphere♪
???لقد نحتت وجهك في كرة الذاكرة؟؟؟
♪Yet gained the wounds I'll always bear♪
???ومع ذلك اكتسبت الجروح التي سأحملها دائمًا؟؟؟
♪That drizzled lane where youth stayed♪
???ذلك الممر الممطر حيث بقي الشباب؟؟؟
♪Our music drew lovers near♪
"موسيقانا جذبت العشاق"
♪At parting pavilion we stared♪
???في جناح الفراق حدقنا؟؟؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
♪Now shadow walks alone in fear♪
???الآن الظل يمشي وحيدًا في خوف؟؟؟
It was my fault.
كانت غلطتي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
♪Red candles count night's vigil sheer♪
???الشموع الحمراء تحسب سهر الليل الشفاف؟؟؟
♪Breaths stretch through passing years♪
???تمتد الأنفاس عبر السنوات الماضية؟؟؟
(I know you still want revenge,)
(أعلم أنك لا تزال تريد الانتقام)
(but I must take you away.)
(ولكن يجب أن آخذك بعيدا.)
♪Dread waking finds this dream unreal♪
???أستيقظ مذعوراً وأجد هذا الحلم غير حقيقي؟؟؟
♪Relentless memory racks with spear♪
???رفوف الذاكرة لا هوادة فيها مع الرمح؟؟؟
♪Fate begins and ends, I sip the past♪
???القدر يبدأ وينتهي، أنا أرتشف الماضي؟؟؟
♪Love and hatred flow endlessly♪
???الحب والكراهية يتدفقان بلا نهاية؟؟؟
♪When spring comes, I see the truth♪
???عندما يأتي الربيع أرى الحقيقة؟؟؟
♪We've changed through the years♪
???لقد تغيرنا عبر السنين؟؟؟
♪Cold lamps reflect pear blossom dew♪
???المصابيح الباردة تعكس ندى زهرة الكمثرى ???
♪Worlds change as streams run west♪
???تتغير العوالم عندما تتدفق المجاري المائية غربًا؟؟؟
♪Rains veil hills, gathering sorrows♪
???أمطار تحجب التلال، وتجمع الأحزان؟؟؟
♪In deep courtyards, hands drift apart♪
???في الساحات العميقة، تتباعد الأيدي؟؟؟